American Association for Labor Legislation Records 5001
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Correspondence, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  March 26-27, 1910
- Correspondence, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  March 28-29, 1910
- Correspondence, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  March 30, 1910
- Correspondence, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  March 31, 1910
- Correspondence, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  April 1-2, 1910
- Correspondence, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  April 3-6, 1910
- Correspondence, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  April 7-9, 1910
- Correspondence, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  April 10-14, 1910
- Correspondence, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  April 15-18, 1910
- Correspondence, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  April 19-21, 1910
- Correspondence, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  April 22-27, 1910
- Correspondence, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  April 28-30, 1910
- Correspondence, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  May 1-5, 1910
- Correspondence, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  May 6-9, 1910
- Correspondence, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  May 10-13, 1910
- Correspondence, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  May 14-16, 1910
- Correspondence, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  May 17-20, 1910
- Correspondence, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  May 21-23, 1910
- Correspondence, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  May 24-25, 1910
- Correspondence, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  May 26-31, 1910
- Correspondence, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  June 1-4, 1910
- Correspondence, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  June 6-7, 1910
- Correspondence, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  June 8-11, 1910
- Correspondence, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  June 12-15, 1910
- Correspondence, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  June 16-18, 1910
- Correspondence, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  June 20-21, 1910
- Correspondence, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  June 22-24, 1910. Includes copy of bulletin in Italian (Ufficio Italiano del Lavoro: Bollettino D'Informazioni)
- Correspondence, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  June 25-27, 1910
- Correspondence, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  June 28-31, 1910
- Correspondence, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  July 1, 2, 4 1910
- Correspondence, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  July 5-7, 1910
- Correspondence, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  July 8-10, 1910
- Correspondence, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  July 11-12, 1910
- Correspondence, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  July 13-14, 1910
- Correspondence, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  July 15-17, 1910
- Correspondence, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  July 18-19, 1910
- Correspondence, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  July 20-21, 1910
- Correspondence, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  July 22, 23, 25, 1910
- Correspondence, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  July 26-27, 1910
- Correspondence, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  July 28-30, 1910
- Correspondence, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  August 1-5, 1910
- Correspondence, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 72)
  August 6-11, 1910
- Correspondence, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 73)
  August 12-16, 1910
- Correspondence, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 74)
  August 17-31, 1910
- Correspondence, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 75)
  September 1910
- Correspondence, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 76)
  October 1-12, 1910
- Correspondence, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 77)
  October 13-20, 1910
- Correspondence, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 78)
  October 21-26, 1910
- Correspondence, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 79)
  October 27-31, 1910
- Correspondence, 1910 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  November 1-2, 1910
- Correspondence, 1910 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  November 3-7, 1910
- Correspondence, 1910 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  November 8-10, 1910
- Correspondence, 1910 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  November 11-14, 1910
- Correspondence, 1910 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  November 15-17, 1910
- Correspondence, 1910 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  November 18-21, 1910
- Correspondence, 1910 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  November 22-24, 1910
- Correspondence, 1910 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  November 25-31, 1910
- Correspondence, 1910 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  December 1-3, 1910
- Correspondence, 1910 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  December 4-7, 1910
- Correspondence, 1910 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  December 8-9, 1910
- Correspondence, 1910 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  December 10-12, 1910
- Correspondence, 1910 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  December 13-16, 1910
- Correspondence, 1910 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  December 17-20, 1910
- Correspondence, 1910 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  December 21-23, 1910
- Correspondence, 1910 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  December 24-27, 1910
- Correspondence, 1910 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  December 28-31, 1910
- Correspondence, 1910 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  January 1-5, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  January 6-8, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  January 9-10, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  January 11-13, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  January 14-16, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  January 17-18, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  January 19-21, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  January 22-24, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  January 25-26, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  January 27-28, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  January 29-31, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  February 1-3, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  February 4-6, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  February 7-8, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  February 9-10, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  February 11-15, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  February 16-17, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  February 18-20, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  February 21-24, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  February 25-27, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  February 28, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  March 1-3, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  March 4, 6, and 7, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  March 8-9, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  March 10-12, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  March 13-15, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  March 16-17, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  March 18-20, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  March 21-23, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  March 24-26, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  March 27-31, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  April 1-4, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  April 5-7, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  April 8-10, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  April 11-13, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  April 14-17, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  April 19-23, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  April 24-26, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  April 27-30, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  May 1-2, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  May 3-5, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  May 6-8, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  May 9-11, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 3, Folder 62)
  May 12-14, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 3, Folder 63)
  May 16-17, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 3, Folder 64)
  May 18-20, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 3, Folder 65)
  May 22-24, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 3, Folder 66)
  May 25-27, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 3, Folder 67)
  May 29-31, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  June 1-5, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  June 6-7, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  June 8-12, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  June 13-15, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  June 16-19, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  June 20-22, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  June 23-27, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  June 28-30, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  July 1-5, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  July 6-8, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  July 10-13, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  July 14-17, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  July 18-20, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  July 21, 22, and 24, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  July 25-28 and 31, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  August 1-3, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  August 4-5, 7-8 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  August 9-12, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  August 14-17, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  August 18-19, 21-22 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  August 23-25, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  August 28-31, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  September 1-3, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  September 4-6, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  September 7-9, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  September 11-12, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  September 13-15, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  September 16-18, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  September 19-21, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  September 22-25, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  September 26-27, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  September 28-30, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  October 1-3, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  October 4-7, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  October 8-12, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  October 13-15, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  October 16-17, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  October 18-19, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  October 20-23, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  October 24-25, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  October 26-27, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  October 28, 30-31 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  November 1-2, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  November 3-7, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  November 8-11, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  November 13-14, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  November 15-16, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  November 17-20, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  November 21-22, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  November 23-24, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  November 25-27, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  November 28. 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  November 29-30, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  December 1-2, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  December 4-5, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  December 6-7, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  December 8-9, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  December 10-11, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  December 12-13, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  December 14-15, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  December 16 and 18, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  December 19-20, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 4, Folder 63)
  December 21-22, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 4, Folder 64)
  December 23-26, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 4, Folder 65)
  December 27-28, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 4, Folder 66)
  December 29-30, 1911
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 4, Folder 67)
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 4, Folder 68)
  January 1-3, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 4, Folder 69)
  January 4-6, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 4, Folder 70)
  January 8-11, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 4, Folder 71)
  January 12-14, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 4, Folder 72)
  January 15-17, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 4, Folder 73)
  January 18-20, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 4, Folder 74)
  January 21-23, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 4, Folder 75)
  January 24-27 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 4, Folder 76)
  January 29-31, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 4, Folder 77)
  February 1-2, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 4, Folder 78)
  February 3-5, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 4, Folder 79)
  February 6-7, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 4, Folder 80)
  February 8-9, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 4, Folder 81)
  February 10-14, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 4, Folder 82)
  February 15-18, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 4, Folder 83)
  February 19-21, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 4, Folder 84)
  February 22-24, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 4, Folder 85)
  February 25-27, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 4, Folder 86)
  February 28-29, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  March 1-2, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  March 3-5, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  March 6, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  March 7, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  March 8-10, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  March 11-12, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  March 13, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  March 14-15, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  March 16 and 18, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  March 19-20, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  March 21-24, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  March 25-27, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  March 28-30, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  April 1-2, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  April 3-4, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  April 5-7, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  April 8-9, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  April 10-11, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  April 12-13, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  April 14-16, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  April 17-19, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  April 20, 22, 23, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  April 24-25, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  April 26-27, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  April 28-30, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  May 1-2, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  May 3-6, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  May 7-9, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  May 10-12, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  May 13-14, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  May 15-16, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  May 17-18, 20, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  May 21-24, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  May 25-31, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  June 1-3, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  June 4-6, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  June 7-10, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  June 11-14, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  June 15-18, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  June 19-22, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  June 23-25, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  June 26-27, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  June 28-29, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  July 1-5, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  July 6-8, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  July 9-11, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  July 12-14, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  July 15-16, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  July 17-21, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  July 22-31, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  August 1-6, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  August 7-8, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  August 9-14, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  August 15-18, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  August 19-22, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 56)
  August 23-31, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  September 1-10, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  September 11-19, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 59)
  September 20-25, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 60)
  September 26-31, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 61)
  October 1-2, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 62)
  October 3-4, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 63)
  October 5-7, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 64)
  October 8-9, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 65)
  October 10-11, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 66)
  October 12-14, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 67)
  October 15-16, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 68)
  October 17-18, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 69)
  October 19-21, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 70)
  October 22-23, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 71)
  October 24-16, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 72)
  October 28-29, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 73)
  October 30-31, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 74)
  November 1-3, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 75)
  November 4-7, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 76)
  November 8-11, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 77)
  November 12, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 78)
  November 13-14, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 79)
  November 15-18, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 80)
  November 19-20, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 81)
  November 21, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 82)
  November 22, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 83)
  November 23-24, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 84)
  November 25, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 85)
  November 26-27, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 86)
  November 28-29, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 87)
  November 30, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  December 1-3, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  December 4-5, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  December 6, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  December 7-9, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  December 10-11, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  December 12-13, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  December 14-15, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  December 16-17, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  December 18, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  December 19-20, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  December 21, 23 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  December 24-26, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  December 27-29, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  December 30-31, 1912
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  No Specific Date
- Correspondence, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  January 1-2, 1913
- Correspondence, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  January 3-4, 1913
- Correspondence, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  January 5-6, 1913
- Correspondence, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  January 7-8, 1913
- Correspondence, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  January 9-11, 1913
- Correspondence, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  January 12-15, 1913
- Correspondence, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  January 16-18, 1913
- Correspondence, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  January 19-21, 1913
- Correspondence, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  January 21-23, 1913
- Correspondence, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  January 24-27, 1913
- Correspondence, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  January 27-28, 1913
- Correspondence, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  January 28-29, 1913
- Correspondence, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  January 29-31, 1913
- Correspondence, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  February 1-3, 1913
- Correspondence, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  February 4, 1913
- Correspondence, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  February 5-6, 1913
- Correspondence, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  February 7-9, 1913
- Correspondence, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  February 10, 1913
- Correspondence, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  February 11, 1913
- Correspondence, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  February 12-13, 1913
- Correspondence, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  February 14-15, 1913
- Correspondence, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  February 16-17, 1913
- Correspondence, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  February 18, 1913
- Correspondence, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  February 19, 1913
- Correspondence, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  February 20, 1913
- Correspondence, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  February 21-23, 1913
- Correspondence, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  February 24-25, 1913
- Correspondence, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  February 26, 1913
- Correspondence, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  February 27, 1913
- Correspondence, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  February 28-29, 1913
- Correspondence, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  March 1-4, 1913
- Correspondence, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  March 5-6, 1913
- Correspondence, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  March 7-8, 1913
- Correspondence, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  March 9-10, 1913
- Correspondence, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  March 11-12, 1913
- Correspondence, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  March 13-14, 1913
- Correspondence, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  March 15-17, 1913
- Correspondence, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  March 18-19, 1913
- Correspondence, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  March 20-21, 1913
- Correspondence, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  March 22-25, 1913
- Correspondence, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 56)
  March 26-27, 1913
- Correspondence, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  March 28-30, 1913
- Correspondence, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 58)
  March 31, 1913
- Correspondence, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 59)
  April 1-2, 1913
- Correspondence, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 60)
  April 3-4, 1913
- Correspondence, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 61)
  April 5-7, 1913
- Correspondence, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 62)
  April 7-9, 1913
- Correspondence, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 63)
  April 10-12, 1913
- Correspondence, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 64)
  April 14, 1913
- Correspondence, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 65)
  April 15, 1913
- Correspondence, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 66)
  April 16, 1913
- Correspondence, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 67)
  April 17, 1913
- Correspondence, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 68)
  April 18-20, 1913
- Correspondence, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 69)
  April 21, 1913
- Correspondence, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 70)
  April 22, 1913
- Correspondence, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 71)
  April 23-24, 1913
- Correspondence, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 72)
  April 25-27, 1913
- Correspondence, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 73)
  April 28-30, 1913
- Correspondence, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 74)
  May 1-2, 1913
- Correspondence, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 75)
  May 2-3, 1913
- Correspondence, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 76)
  May 5-6, 1913
- Correspondence, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 77)
  May 7, 1913
- Correspondence, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 78)
  May 8-9, 1913
- Correspondence, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 79)
  May 10-12, 1913
- Correspondence, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 80)
  May 13-14, 1913
- Correspondence, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 81)
  May 15-17, 1913
- Correspondence, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 82)
  May 18-21, 1913
- Correspondence, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 83)
  May 22-24, 1913
- Correspondence, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 84)
  May 26-27, 1913
- Correspondence, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 85)
  May 28-29, 1913
- Correspondence, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 86)
  May 30-31, 1913
- Correspondence, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 87)
  June 1-3, 1913
- Correspondence, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 88)
  June 4-5, 1913
- Correspondence, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 89)
  June 6-9, 1913
- Correspondence, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 90)
  June 10-12, 1913
- Correspondence, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 91)
  June 13-14, 1913
- Correspondence, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 92)
  June 15-16, 1913
- Correspondence, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 93)
  June 17-19, 1913
- Correspondence, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  June 20, 1913